Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Annual reports, degree files, and indexes maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1900-1976; Accession 1978-A-008
  - Annual Reports
    - 1974-1975
      - Astronomy, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Athletics, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 87)
      - Behavioral Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Berkeley College, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - British Art Center, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Calhoun College, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 88)
      - Career Advisory Service, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Cell Biology, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Chemistry, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Child Study Center, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 89)
      - Classics, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Comparative Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Computer Science, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Council on East Asian Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Dermatology, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 90)
      - Diagnostic Radiology, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Divinity School, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Drama, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Timothy Dwight College, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 91)
      - Economic Growth Center, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Economics, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Jonathan Edwards College, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 92)
      - Engineering and Applied Science, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - English, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 93)
      - Geology and Geophysics, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 94)
      - Germanic Languages, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Health Services, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 95)
      - History, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - History of Art, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 96)
      - History of Science and Medicine, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Human Genetics, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Internal Medicine, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 97)
      - International and Area Studies, Concilium on, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 98)
      - Language Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 99)
      - Laboratory Medicine, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Law School, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Library, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Linguistics, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Mathematics, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 100)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - Music, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 101)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 102)
      - Neurology, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Nursing, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 103)
      - Ophthalmology, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Organization and Management, School of, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Pathology, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 104)
      - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Peabody Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Pediatrics, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 105)
      - Pharmacology, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Philosophy, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Physical Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Physics, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Physiology, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 106)
      - Political Science, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Police, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Psychiatry, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 107)
      - Psychology, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Religious Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 108)
      - Saybrook College, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 109)
      - Seven Springs Center, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Silliman College, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Social and Policy Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Sociology, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Spanish and Portuguese, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Ezra Stiles College, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 110)
      - Summer Language Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Therapeutic Radiology, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 111)
      - Trumbull College, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
      - Yale College, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 112)
  - Subject Files
    - Activities - Newspaper clippings
      - 1975 Apr-Jun (Box 17, Folder 113)
      - 1975 Jan-Mar (Box 17, Folder 114)
      - 1974 Oct-Dec (Box 17, Folder 115)
      - 1974 Jul-Sep (Box 17, Folder 116)
      - 1974 Apr-Jun (Box 17, Folder 117)
      - 1974 Jan-Mar (Box 17, Folder 118)
      - 1973 Oct-Dec (Box 17, Folder 119)
      - 1973 Jul-Sep (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - African Famine Relief Organization, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - A.I.E.S.E.C., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - Alumni Fund, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Annual Report - Dept. of Athletics, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 124)
    - Awareness Day, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 125)
    - Chapel-Howe Project, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Child Study Center, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 129)
    - College Transfers, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 130)
    - Colleges, Jonathan Edwards - Photo, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 131)
    - Colleges, Masters and Deans, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    - Commencement, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 133)
    - Community problems: Ascertainment, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    - Compensatory Education, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 135)
    - Connecticut Conference of Mayors, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - Connecticut Elderly Nutrition Project, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - Council on Community Affairs, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Council of University Institutes for Urban Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - Dwight St., 253-285, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    - Economic - Financial, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 143)
    - Education Group, Community, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - Educational Consortium, Yale-New Haven, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - Educational - Cultural, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Elementary Education, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - Enlightenment, Fourth International Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Facilities for City Personnel, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - Facilities for New Haven Community, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - Faculty Directory, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - Graduate and Professional Students proposed Extension School, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Grievance Ad Hoc Group, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - Health - Medical, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Health Care Inc., New Haven, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - Housing Authority, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 162)
    - Ideas for the Future, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 163)
    - Industrial Development Group, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - Insurance, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - Junior Science and Humanities Symposium, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 166)
    - Lee, Richard C., 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - Legal Assistance Association, New Haven, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Lewis-Farmington Fellowship, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - Library, Yale, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - Locations, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    - Lovett's Sermon, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1976 (Box 19, Folder 174)
      - 1975 (Box 20, Folder 175)
      - 1974 (Box 20, Folder 176 - 179)
      - 1974 (cont'd) (Box 21, Folder 180)
      - 1973 (Box 21, Folder 181 - 182)
    - New Haven Statistics (Box 21, Folder 183 - 184)
    - Newspaper Organizing Group, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 185)
    - Nuts and Cranks (Box 22, Folder 186 - 187)
    - Olympics 1984, Community Relations, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 188)
    - Orange Incident, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 189)
    - Physical Plant, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 190)
    - Publicity, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 191)
    - Receipts, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - Relations, Yale-New Haven, Report, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 195)
    - Relations, Yale-New Haven, Report, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Relations, Yale-Mew Haven, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - "Report of the Commission to Study Yale", 1959 (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Report of the Treasurer, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - Schay, Dan, "New Haven for Yale Students", 1974 (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Security, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Security, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Security, 1074-1977 (Box 23, Folder 203)
    - Security Committee Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 204)
    - Senior citizens' Outing, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 205)
    - Services, Payment for, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 206)
    - Spanish-Speaking Students, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 207)
    - Student Community Housing Corporation, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 208)
    - Suggestions, Community Affairs, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 209)
    - Summer Academic Programs, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 210)
    - Summer Term, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 211)
    - [Superdude], 1973 (Box 24, Folder 212)
    - Tickets, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 213)
    - Tours, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 214)
    - Transit Study Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 215)
    - Undergraduate Information, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 216)
    - United States Youth Games, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 217)
    - Urban Academy, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 218)
    - Urban Affairs - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - Urban Involvement of Higher Education, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - Urban Studies, Institute of, University of Texas, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - Vaisnys, Elona - New Haven Register, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 222)
    - Volunteer, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 223)
    - Volunteer Services: Mid-Year Report, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 224)
    - Volunteer Services: Budgets, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 225)
    - Volunteer Services: Budgets, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 226)
    - Wards
      - I. Foltz (Box 25, Folder 227)
      - 10. Fasulo (Box 25, Folder 236)
      - 11, Fenders (Box 25, Folder 237)
      - 16. Longyear (Box 25, Folder 242)
      - 17. Dynia (Box 25, Folder 243)
      - 18. Logue (Box 25, Folder 244)
      - 19. Claxton (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 257)
    - West Haven, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 258)
    - White Paper, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 259)
    - Wilder Report, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 260)
    - Wilder Update Crosscheck, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 261)
    - Wilder Report, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 262)
    - Yale Amateur Radio Club, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 263)
    - Yale Art School, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 264)
    - Yale Booth, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 265)
    - Yale Promenade, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 266)
    - Yale Related Activities, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 267)
  - Council of Masters
    - 1932 Nov 1 - 1937 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 268 - 269)
    - 1932 Mar 18 - 1938 Oct 26 (Box 27, Folder 270 - 272)
    - 1937 Oct 22 - 1939 May 26 (Box 28, Folder 273 - 274)
    - 1939 Oct 20 -1941 May 2 (Box 28, Folder 275)
    - 1941 Oct 3 - 1943 Apr 30 (Box 28, Folder 276 - 277)
    - 1943 Jul 2 - 1945 Jun 6 (Box 28, Folder 278 - 279)
    - 1945 Sep 25 - 1947 Jun 6 (Box 29, Folder 280 - 281)
    - 1948 Oct - 1949 Apr (Box 29, Folder 282 - 283)
    - 1949 Oct 7 - 1951 Jun 1 (Box 29, Folder 284 - 285)
    - 1950 - 1960 Jun 3 (Box 29, Folder 286)
    - 1951 Sep 21 - 1953 Jun 19 (Box 30, Folder 287 - 288)
    - 1953 Oct 2 - 1955 Jun 3 (Box 30, Folder 289 - 290)
    - 1955 Sep 30 - 1957 Jun 4 (Box 30, Folder 291 - 292)
    - 1957 Sep 27 - 1960 Jun 3 (Box 30, Folder 293 - 294)
    - 1960 Sep 30 - 1962 Mar 2 (Box 31, Folder 295)
    - 1962 Oct 5 - 1964 May 29 (Box 31, Folder 296)
    - 1964 Oct 2 - 1966 May 20 (Box 31, Folder 297 - 298)
    - 1960 Sep 30 - 1967 May 26 Index (Box 31, Folder 299)
    - 1966 Sep 23 - 1967 May 26 (Box 31, Folder 300)
    - 1967 Oct 27 - 1968 May 24 (Box 32, Folder 301)
    - 1968 Sep 27 - 1969 Dec 5 (Box 32, Folder 302 - 303)
    - 1970 Apr 24 (Box 32, Folder 304)
  - Index Records
    - Governing Board A-Z, undated (Box 34)
    - Invitations A-R, 1930-1960 (Box 35)
    - Student Withdrawals A-G, undated (Box 35)
    - Presidential
      - A-Cop, undated (Box 36)
      - Cr-Hi, undated (Box 37)
      - Ho-Mo, undated (Box 38)
      - Mu-Sm, undated (Box 39)
      - Sn-Z, undated (Box 40)
  - Degree Records
    - 1909 (Box 41, Folder 305)
    - 1910 (Box 41, Folder 306)
    - 1911 (Box 41, Folder 307)
    - 1912 (Box 41, Folder 308)
    - 1913 (Box 41, Folder 309)
    - 1914 (Box 41, Folder 310)
    - 1915 (Box 41, Folder 311)
    - 1916 (Box 41, Folder 312)
    - 1917 (Box 41, Folder 313)
    - 1918 (Box 41, Folder 314)
    - 1919 (Box 41, Folder 315)
    - 1920 (Box 41, Folder 316)
    - 1921 (Box 41, Folder 317)
    - 1922 (Box 41, Folder 318)
    - 1923 (Box 41, Folder 319)
    - 1928 (Box 41, Folder 320)
    - 1929 (Box 41, Folder 321)
    - 1930 (Box 41, Folder 322)
    - 1931 (Box 42, Folder 323)
    - 1932 (Box 42, Folder 324)
    - 1933 (Box 42, Folder 325)
    - 1934 (Box 42, Folder 326)
    - 1935 (Box 42, Folder 327)
    - 1936 (Box 42, Folder 328)
    - 1937 (Box 42, Folder 329)
    - 1938 (Box 42, Folder 330)
    - 1939 (Box 42, Folder 331)
    - 1940 (Box 42, Folder 332)
    - 1941 (Box 42, Folder 333)
    - 1942 (Box 42, Folder 334)
    - 1943 (Box 42, Folder 335)
    - 1944 (Box 42, Folder 336)
    - 1955 (Box 43, Folder 337)
    - 1956 (Box 43, Folder 338)
    - 1957 (Box 43, Folder 339)
    - 1958 (Box 43, Folder 340)
    - 1959 (Box 43, Folder 341)
    - 1960 (Box 43, Folder 342 - 343)
    - 1961 (Box 43, Folder 344 - 345)
    - 1962 (Box 43, Folder 346)
    - 1963 (Box 43, Folder 347 - 348)
    - 1964 (Box 43, Folder 349 - 350)
    - 1965 (Box 43, Folder 351 - 352)
    - 1966 (Box 44, Folder 353 - 354)
    - 1967 (Box 45, Folder 355 - 356)
    - 1968 (Box 45, Folder 357 - 358)
    - 1969 (Box 45, Folder 359 - 360)
  - Subject Files
    - Alumni Associations manual, undated (Box 46, Folder 361)
    - Alumni University Day programs, 1914-1961 (Box 46, Folder 362)
    - Anniversary: 250th celebration of Yale, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 363)
    - Architectural plans: Committee on, undated (Box 46, Folder 364 - 365)
    - Art Gallery Associates, 1955-1960 (Box 46, Folder 366)
    - Art Gallery Associates, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 367)
    - Art Gallery Associates, 1965-1969 (Box 46, Folder 368)
    - Art Gallery: Minutes of Governing Board, 1940-1942 (Box 46, Folder 369)
    - Art Gallery: Minutes of Governing Board
      - 1940-1942 (Box 47, Folder 370)
      - 1942-1945 (Box 47, Folder 371 - 372)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 373)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 47, Folder 374 - 375)
      - 1949-1953 (Box 47, Folder 376)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 48, Folder 377)
      - 1954-1957 (Box 48, Folder 378)
      - No date (Box 48, Folder 379)
    - Bergin, T. G.: poetry, 1955-1967 (Box 48, Folder 380 - 381)
    - Chief Marshall, 1959-1968 (Box 48, Folder 382)
    - Chief Marshall, 1969-1972 (Box 48, Folder 383)
    - Colleges at Yale University (Box 48, Folder 384)
    - Conference information, 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 385)
    - Costello, John A,: Address, Prime Minister of Ireland annual dinner of Knights of St. Patrick, 1956 March 18 (Box 48, Folder 386)
    - Educational Investment Plan, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 387)
    - Educational Policy, Committee on
      - 1919-1929 (Box 49, Folder 388)
      - 1929-1939 (Box 49, Folder 389)
      - 1939-1949 (Box 50, Folder 390)
      - 1949-1959 (Box 50, Folder 391)
      - 1959-1969 (Box 50, Folder 392)
      - Committee minutes, 1969 October (Box 50, Folder 393)
    - Emergency Council minutes, 1917-1918 (Box 51, Folder 394)
    - Grace New Haven Community Hospital, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 395)
    - Grace New Haven Community Hospital, 1961-1962 (Box 51, Folder 396)
    - Greetings to other institutions, 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 397)
    - Handbook for class secretaries (Box 51, Folder 398)
    - Institute of Far Eastern Languages, 1956-1962 (Box 52, Folder 403)
    - Inventory of Yale College classrooms, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 404)
    - Invitations: samples of A-G (Box 52, Folder 405 - 410)
    - Invitations: samples of H-S (Box 53, Folder 411 - 416)
    - Invitations: samples of T-Z (Box 54, Folder 417)
    - Lectures and income available, 1945-1957 (Box 54, Folder 418)
    - Lectures: University Committee minutes, 1921, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 419)
    - Libraries (Yale): bookplates (Box 54, Folder 420)
    - Libraries and Museums, Committee on, 1936-1964 (Box 54, Folder 421)
    - Lux et Veritas, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 422)
    - Memorials: minutes of Committee, 1902-1943 (Box 54, Folder 423)
    - Miscellaneous: honorary fellows; masters; lectureships; bursars; Board of Admissions; chairmen; department directors; curators; Yale medals (Box 54, Folder 424)
    - Navy classification of Yale students, 1942-1944 (Box 54, Folder 425)
    - Pageant Committees: minutes, 1915-1916 (Box 55, Folder 426)
    - Peabody Museum: Trustees, 1936-1961 (Box 55, Folder 427)
    - Personnel manual: Interim, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 428)
    - Personnel manual: "Salary Administration supplement", 1972 (Box 55, Folder 429)
    - Preliminary Financial Plan, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 430)
    - President's Committee on Discipline: report (Box 55, Folder 431)
    - Property maps: Yale (Box 55, Folder 432)
    - Publications, Committee on: minutes, 1908-1928 (Box 55, Folder 433)
    - Pusey, Nathan Marsh, President of Harvard University: address made in his honor, 1953 November 20 (Box 55, Folder 434)
    - Salary study information: conference presentation, 1966 October 18 (Box 56, Folder 435)
    - School of University: deans and directors, professorships, 1864-1958 (Box 56, Folder 436)
    - Seals: department and school, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 437)
    - Song Book: Yale Alumni, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 438)
    - Standard operating procedures, 1961-1970 (Box 56, Folder 439 - 442)
    - Survey of nonacademic activities, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 443 - 447)
    - University assemblies, 1942-1957 (Box 57, Folder 449)
    - University Council: Committee on Publications, 1928-1939 (Box 58, Folder 450)
    - University Council: minutes, 1918-1935 (Box 59, Folder 451 - 453)
    - University Council: record, 1900-1917 (Box 60, Folder 454)
    - Vassar-Yale study: departmental reports, 1967 September (Box 61, Folder 455)
    - Yale certificates: samples, Undated (Box 61, Folder 456)
    - "Yale Collections, Other Than Those in The Library and Museums", undated (Box 61, Folder 457)
    - Yale Endowments, 1917 (Box 61, Folder 458)
    - Yale Name, Committee on Protection of: minutes, 1914-1922 (Box 61)
    - Yale Laboratories of Primate Biology, Incorporated, 1935-1956 (Box 62)
  - Audiotapes
    - Brewster, Kingman: Alumni session, 2 audiotapes (reel-to-reel), 1970 June 13 (Box 63, Folder 459 - 460)
    - Brewster, Kingman: Baccalaureate address, 1970 June 7; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 63, Folder 461)
    - Class Day, 1970 June 7; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 63, Folder 462 - 463)
- Records of Wyllys Warner, 1838-1868; Accession 1979-A-012
  - Correspondence regarding honorary degrees, 1859-1868 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Collier, M. Dwight--Scheme for a report on the state of the University, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, documents, and bills, 1838-1866 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and memorabilia of Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1972-1979; Accession 1980-A-013
  - Correspondence
    - A - general (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Data Systems (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Admissions Office, Undergraduate (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Afro-American Historical Society (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Albertus Magnus College (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alumni Fund (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Magazine (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alummi Records (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Records - "400 List" (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Seminar (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Studies Program (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Angell, James Rowland, Mrs. (Katherine) (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Annual reports (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Architecture, School of (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Armory, Yale (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Archives (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Arnstein, report on Buckley (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Art Gallery (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Art Gallery, Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Art Gallery, American Arts Workshop (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Art Gallery, Associates Board of Governors (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Art Gallery Garvan Collection International Silver Company (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Art, School of (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Associate Treasurer's Office (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Astronomy department (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Athletics
      - General (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - General (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Captain's letter (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Cullman Courts (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Coaches (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Directorship (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Golf (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Golf Course Selection Committee (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Hockey (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Hockey search (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Injury information system (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Jones report (Box 2, Folder 39 - 41)
      - Lacrosse (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Nutrition (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Report - Institutional Relations and Alumni Programs (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Soccer (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Soccer - La Crosse Stadium (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Squash (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Tennis (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Tennis coach (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Tennis - Kevin Lynn (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Audio Visual (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - AYA (Association of Yale Alumni) (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Admissions committee report (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Admissions report on undergraduates, 1975 October (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Admissions report on undergraduates, 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Athletics committee (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Athletic report, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - 'Bank" of Alumni names (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Board of Governors Current and Committee Chairman (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Communications Board Directory (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Communications group (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Communications, S. Flink (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Community affairs (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Continuing education of alumni (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Convocation, 1973 October 26 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Convocation Assembly VI (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Convocation Assembly V (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - DKE House (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - General (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - B - general (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - B - general (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Band, Yale (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Banner, Yale (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Battell Chapel (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Beasley, John S, II - Vanderbilt University (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Beer permits (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Beinecke family (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Bergin, Thomas G. (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Berkeley Divinity School (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Better Business Bureau of New Haven (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Biology Department (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Birthday, Yale's 275th (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Black Coalition (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Black student college (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Bowl, Yale (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Branford College (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - "Broadside" (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Buildings and Grounds Committee (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Buildings and Grounds Faculty - Advisory Committee (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Buildings, naming of (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Bursar's employment (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Bursar's Office (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - C - general (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Cairo, American University in (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Calendar, undergraduate and University (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Campus police (Box 5, Folder 99)